rushcard.com 2016-04-11

# Website/Mobile App Privacy Policy | RushCard

**PLEASE READ CAREFULLY BEFORE USING OR ACCESSING THIS WEBSITE. BY ACCESSING THIS WEBSITE YOU ARE INDICATING YOUR ACKNOWLEDGMENT AND ACCEPTANCE OF THESE TERMS.**

The following Website/Mobile App Privacy Policy (“Website Privacy Policy”) apply to the RushCard websites (each, a “Site” and collectively, the “Sites”) owned and operated by UniRush, LLC, and its subsidiaries and affiliates (collectively, “UniRush,” “we,” or “us”) and does not modify your Cardholder Agreement which governs your use of your Prepaid Visa RushCard (“Card”).  By accessing or using the Sites, whether via computer, mobile device or other technology, you represent that you have read and agree to this Website Privacy Policy in their entirety.  If you do not agree to this Website Privacy Policy, do not use the Sites. UniRush is free to revise Website Privacy Policy at any time by updating this posting, and your use after such change signifies your acceptance of the changed terms.  Please check this Website Privacy Policy periodically for changes.

## The Information We Collect

We collect both personal and non-personal information from you online.

For the purpose of this Website Privacy Policy, when we use the term “personal information” we mean information that is collected in conjunction with your name.  We typically collect such information by requesting that you complete an online application.  When we use the term “non-personal information” we mean information that is not collected in conjunction with your name.  We may use the following technologies to collect such information:

  * Cookies.  Many sites use “cookies,” which are small text files that reside on your computer to identify you as a unique user.  We may use cookies on our Sites to allow us to, among other things, measure activity and to personalize your experience.  For instance, cookies may enable us to remember your viewing preferences without requiring you to re-type a user name and password.  Cookies may also allow us to track your status or progress when requesting products, services, or information.  If you choose, you can set your browser to reject cookies or you can manually delete individual or all of the cookies on your computer by following your browser’s help file directions.  However, if your browser is set to reject cookies or you manually delete cookies, you may have some trouble accessing and using some of the pages and features that are currently on our Sites, or that we may put on our Sites in the future.
  * Web Beacons.  A web beacon is an electronic file on a Web page that allows us to count and recognize users who have visited that page.  Among other things, a web beacon can be used in HTML-formatted email to determine responses to our communications and measure their effectiveness.  You can generally avoid web beacons in email by turning off HTML display and displaying only the text portion of your email.
  * Internet Protocol (IP) Address.  As you enter our Sites, we capture and retain the IP address of the device you are using, such as a personal computer or a mobile device.
  * Location and Usage Information.  If you use our mobile application or access our website using a mobile device, we may collect information concerning your location, information about when an App is launched, individual session lengths for Apps, or why an App may not be working. 

Do Not Track Header:  Some web browsers and devices permit you to broadcast a preference that you not be “tracked” online.  At this time we do not modify your experience based upon whether such a signal is broadcast.

## How We Use Personal Information

Our primary purpose in collecting information about you is to provide you with products, services, and information that we think may be of interest to you.  We may also decide to use information about you to track how you use our Sites.  In addition, we may aggregate the information that you provide with the information that other users provide in order to conduct research, analysis, or studies for our own purposes (i.e., not related to providing you with specific products or services).

We may decide to send people who provide us with their email addresses email.  If you decide that you do not want to receive commercial emails from us, you can “opt-out” from receiving such emails by clicking on the “unsubscribe” link provided at the bottom of every commercial email.  Please note that if you choose to opt-out, we will still send you e-mail relating to specific products or services that you purchase, or e-mail that we believe is pertinent to any communication that you have sent to us, or relationship that you may have with us.  If you decide at a later time that you would like to receive commercial emails from us, you can re-add yourself to our communication list.

We may share personal information or non-personal information with other companies in the following situations:

  * Sharing Your Information with Service Providers.  We may share information with companies or individuals that provide us with services.  These services may include, among other things, helping us to provide services that you request, to create or maintain our databases, to research and analyze the people who request products, services or information from us, to prepare and distribute communications, or to respond to inquiries.  Any party with whom we share your personal information is required either contractually or by law to keep it confidential and not to disclose it without your consent and to only use such information as required for the services to be performed.
  * Other Companies: We may provide information to carefully selected outside companies when we believe their products or services may be of interest to you.
  * Law Enforcement and Legal Process.  We may disclose personal information to government and regulatory agencies to comply with a lawful summons, court order, subpoena, discovery request, fraud investigation, audit, regulatory examination or other valid court, government, or regulatory agency request.
  * Business Transition.  In the event that we, or any portion of our assets, are acquired your information may be transferred to the acquiring company.

Behavioral Advertisers.  We may participate in behavioral-based advertising.  This means that a third party may use technology, such as a cookie on your browser or a web beacon, to identify you on our Sites so that they can provide advertising about products and services tailored to your interest.  That advertising may appear either on our Sites, or on other websites.  If you would like to opt-out of behavioral advertising based on your use of our Sites, you can do so by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative at [www.networkadvertising.org](http://www.networkadvertising.org/) and the Digital Advertising Alliance at [www.aboutads.info](http://www.aboutads.info/).

Other Websites.  Our Sites, e-mails, or applications may link to third parties’ websites.  It is also possible that third parties’ websites or e-mails may link to our Sites.  We are not responsible for the content or the privacy practices employed by third parties.  We encourage you to read the privacy policies of these websites before transmitting any personal identifiable information to third parties.

## How We Secure Information

We use reasonable measures to help keep information secure, and to help prevent it from becoming disclosed to individuals who are not described in this Website Privacy Policy.  While we follow reasonable procedures to try to protect the information in our possession, no security system is perfect and we cannot promise, and you should not expect, that your information will remain secure in all circumstances.

## How We Communicate With You

If you have any questions or concerns regarding anything contained herein, please contact us at:

UniRush, LLC

4701 Creek Road

Cincinnati, OH 45242

Email: [agent@rushcard.com](mailto:agent@rushcard.com)

For your security, please do not email us personal information via e-mail, including:

Your 16 digit Account number

Your Social Security Number

Your Date of Birth

Your RushCard online account login info (Username or Password)

Your State Issued ID

If we need, or are required, to contact you concerning any event that involves your information we may do so by email, telephone, or mail.

We may change the Website/Mobile App Privacy Policy any time without prior notice. Please review the latest version online at [https://www.rushcard.com](https://www.rushcard.com/).

We have a process in place that helps us to maintain the accuracy of the personally identifiable information that we collect.  Please visit [https://www.rushcard.com](https://www.rushcard.com/) to review and correct information about yourself, such as a change in your name or contact information.  If you believe that our information is inaccurate or incomplete, you also can contact us at the number or address listed above and ask us to correct or update our information.

## Your California Privacy Rights

Under California Civil Code sections 1798.83-1798.84, California residents are entitled to ask us for a notice describing what categories of personal customer information we share with third parties or corporate affiliates for those third parties or corporate affiliates’ direct marketing purposes.  That notice will identify the categories of information shared and will include a list of the third parties and affiliates with which it was shared, along with their names and addresses.  If you are a California resident and would like a copy of this notice, please submit a written request to the following address:

UniRush, LLC  
P.O. Box 42482  
Cincinnati, OH 45242

Last Revised: August, 2014

The Prepaid Visa RushCard is issued by MetaBank®, Member FDIC, pursuant to a license from Visa U.S.A. Inc.

***** When you Direct Deposit $3,000 or more in combined tax refunds from the US Department of the Treasury or from your local or state tax agencies, you will receive a $30 account credit. When you Direct Deposit between $2,000 and $2,999 in combined tax refunds from the US Department of the Treasury or from your local or state tax agencies, you will receive a $20 account credit. If you Direct Deposit $2,000 - $2,999 and then later Direct Deposit an additional amount from the US Department of Treasury or from your local or state tax agencies which brings your total combined deposited tax refund amount to more than $3,000, you will receive an additional $10 account credit. Limit one offer per customer. Account will be credited within 30 days after qualifying deposit. The card account must be in good standing at the time the credit is given, meaning your RushCard is not dormant, blocked, revoked or closed. Offer is void where prohibited. Offer expires 5/15/2016. This optional offer is not a MetaBank product or service and MetaBank does not endorse it.

**†** Faster access to funds is based on comparison of a paper check versus electronic Direct Deposit.

  1. Important information for opening a card account: To help the federal government fight the funding of terrorism and money laundering activities, the USA PATRIOT Act requires all financial institutions and their third parties to obtain, verify, and record information that identifies each person who opens a card account. What this means for you: When you open a card account, we will ask for your name, address, date of birth, and other information that will allow us to identify you. We may also ask to see your driver's license or other identifying documents.
  2. Getting your money up to two days sooner is based on comparison of traditional banking policies and deposit of paper checks from employers and government agencies versus electronic direct deposits. Many employers and government agencies notify us of direct deposits before your "official" day scheduled for payment. If we receive early notice, we may load your direct deposit earlier than your "official" day scheduled for payment. We may limit the amount or type of Direct Deposit eligible for early loading.
  3. There is no charge for Rush Text alerts; however, standard text message and data rates, fees, and charges may apply. Charges are dependent on your service plan, which may include fees from your carrier to send and receive text messages. Charges will appear on your wireless bill or be deducted from your prepaid phone balance. Message frequency will be determined by the alert options you select. For more information, refer to our RushTEXT terms under My Contact Preferences in the online account or text the word "HELP" to 697874 (MYRUSH). To unsubscribe, text the word "STOP" to 697874 (MYRUSH).
  4. The combined total of Transaction Fees and International Transaction Fees is limited to $10.00 in each calendar month and is based on the date the transaction is posted to your card account as reflected on your statement.
  5. Maintenance Fee assessed if no Card Transactions or loads onto a Card have occurred for a period of ninety (90) consecutive days. Maintenance Fee is assessed each month and will be deducted from your Card balance until you next use your Card.
  6. Cash loading not available at Walmarts in VT. Check loading not available at Walmarts in NJ, NY, RI, VT.
  7. The Visa Zero Liability policy covers U.S.–issued cards only and does not apply to ATM transactions, PIN transactions not processed by Visa, or certain commercial card transactions. Cardholder must notify issuer promptly of any unauthorized use. Consult issuer for additional details or visit [www.visa.com/security](http://www.visa.com/security).
  8. If you add money to your RushCard prior to setting up a PIN, you will not be able to access that money until you set up a PIN.
  9. This is not a credit card.
  10. Your Prepaid Card account and associated direct deposit account number cannot be used for preauthorized direct debits from merchants or from utility or Internet service providers. If presented for payment, these preauthorized direct debits will be declined and your payment to the merchant or provider will not be processed. The bank routing number and direct deposit account number are for the purpose of initiating direct deposits to your Prepaid Card account only. You are not authorized to provide this bank routing number and direct deposit account number to anyone other than your employer or payer. Direct deposit capability is subject to payer’s support of this feature. Check with your payer to find out when the direct deposit of funds will start. Funds availability is subject to timing of payer’s funding.
  11. "Out-of-network" refers to all ATMs outside of the MoneyPass ATM network. Certain fees including those assessed by the ATM owner/operator may apply. See Cardholder Agreement for complete details. 
  12. Subject to gas station’s terms, conditions, and limitations. The gas station may place a temporary hold on your available balance of up to $75 or more. The merchant will release the temporary hold when the transaction has been paid and replace it with the actual amount of your gasoline purchase. If applicable, the pump will automatically stop dispensing gasoline when the purchase reaches your card account balance (if you are on the Pay As You Go plan, the $1.00 Transaction Fee will be subtracted from your card account balance). To avoid this hold, pay inside and tell the cashier exactly how much you want to spend.
  13. All checks are subject to approval by Ingo in its sole discretion. Fees and other terms and conditions apply to check load services. Visit [ingomoney.com/tc.html](http://ingomoney.com/tc.html) for complete details. The Ingo Money service is provided by Ingo Money, Inc. and First Century Bank, N.A. Use of Ingo Money is subject to Ingo Money and First Century Bank Terms & Conditions, and the information you send is subject to the terms of the Ingo Money Privacy Policy. Approval review usually takes 3 to 5 minutes, but may take up to one hour. All checks are subject to approval for funding in Ingo Money’s sole discretion. Approved printed payroll and government checks can be funded to your card in minutes for a fee of 1% of the check value. All other check types may be funded in minutes for 4% of check value. There is a minimum fee of $5 for all checks approved and funded in minutes. Funds from approved checks may be loaded in 10 days at no charge provided the check does not return unpaid in the 10-day period. Unapproved checks will not be loaded to your card. Ingo Money reserves the right to recover funds from bad checks if you knew the check was bad when you submitted it, if you attempt to cash or deposit it elsewhere after funding or if you otherwise act illegally or fraudulently. Fees may apply for loading or use of your card. Contact your card issuer for details.
  14. Through the Refer-a-Friend program, cardholders and a referred friend will receive a $20 load to their card accounts if the referred friend applies for a RushCard, activates and loads the card. In order for both the cardholder and friend to receive a $20 load on the card account, the friend must apply for a RushCard using the referral code provided by the RushCard cardholder, activate the card, and make a load of $20 onto the card. The Refer-a-Friend program is available for all active RushCard members in good standing. RushCard's Refer-a-Friend program is limited to referring new card members only; current members cannot refer themselves or other current card members. Card members can earn a maximum of $500 per year with the Refer-a-Friend program.
  15. This optional offer is not a MetaBank® product or service nor does MetaBank endorse this offer.
  16. While this specific feature is available for free, certain other transaction fees and costs, terms, and conditions are associated with the use of this Card. See the [Cardholder Agreement](https://www.rushcard.com/legal/cardholder-agreement) for more details.

CONSENT FOR THE ELECTRONIC DISCLOSURE OF INFORMATION

Please read this Consent for the Electronic Disclosure of Information carefully and keep a copy for your records. You should not open a card account from a public computer.

The following disclosures are required by the federal Electronic Signatures in Global and National Commerce Act (“E-SIGN”). In order to open a Prepaid Visa RushCard® (the “Card Account”) electronically, you must acknowledge receipt of these disclosures, agree that you have read the disclosures and consent for the electronic delivery of all statements, disclosures and notices. We may amend or change the terms and conditions of this Consent for the Electronic Disclosure of Information at any time. For the latest version, please review online at [www.rushcard.com](http://www.rushcard.com/).

Consent for the Electronic Disclosure of Information

By clicking the box corresponding to the Consent for Electronic Disclosure of Information on the application submission page, you acknowledge receipt of the E-Sign Disclosure and Consent, that you have read the Consent for Electronic Disclosure of Information and you affirmatively consent to the electronic receipt of any and all statements, disclosures, notices, terms and conditions, and other documents, and all subsequent changes thereto, related to the Card Account (collectively, “Statements”). We will provide subsequent disclosures to your email. Please be sure your email address and other contact information is correct by visiting our website at [www.rushcard.com](http://www.rushcard.com/) or calling us at 1-866-787-4227. 

After you consent to the electronic receipt of statements and activate your RushCard, Statements and your available card balance are available at no additional cost online at [www.rushcard.com](http://www.rushcard.com/) or by calling 1-866-787-4227. You agree that we do not need to provide you with a written (non-electronic) copy of any Statement, unless you specifically request us to send you a copy. There is a fee of $1.00 dollar to receive a paper statement in the mail.

Paper Delivery of Disclosures and Notices

You may choose to have a paper copy of any particular Statement mailed to you by contacting us by phone at 1-866 787-4227, by facsimile at 1-866-931-7874, electronically at [agent@rushcard.com](mailto:agent@rushcard.com) or you may write to the Program Provider via mail at UniRush LLC, P.O. Box 42482, Cincinnati, OH 45242. Be sure to state that you are requesting a paper copy of a particular Statement. There is a $1.00 Paper Statement Fee for this service assessed each time a paper copy of any Statement is mailed to you.

System Requirements to Access Information

In order to access, receive and retain Statements electronically, you must provide at your own expense an Internet connected device that is compatible at the time of such access with the minimum requirements outlined below. 

To receive Statements electronically, you must have the following equipment and software:

  * A personal computer or other device which is capable of accessing the Internet. Your access to this page verifies that your system/device meets the requirements.
  * An Internet web browser capable of supporting 128-bit SSL encrypted communications, which requires a minimum web browser version of either Microsoft® Internet Explorer version 6.0 (available for downloading at [Microsoft](http://www.microsoft.com/windows/ie/downloads/default.asp)) and your system or device must have 128-bit SSL encryption software. Your access to this page verifies that your browser and encryption software/device meet the requirements.
  * You must have software which permits you to receive and access Portable Document Format or “PDF” files, such as Adobe Acrobat Reader® version 8.0 and above (available for downloading at [Adobe](http://www.adobe.com/products/acrobat/readstep2.html)). Your access to this page verifies that your system/device has the necessary software to permit you to receive and access PDF files.

System Requirements to Retain Information

To retain a copy of a Statement, your device must have the ability to download and store PDF files.

Statements in Writing

All Statements in either electronic or paper format are in writing. Please print or download for your records a copy of this disclosure and other Statements.

Federal Law

You acknowledge and agree that your consent for the electronic disclosure of Statements is provided in connection with a transaction in or affecting interstate commerce that is subject to and governed by the federal Electronic Signatures in Global and National Commerce Act. 

Withdrawal of Consent for Electronic Delivery of Information

You may withdraw your consent to receive any future Statement electronically by contacting us by phone at 1-866 787-4227, by withdrawing your consent online via the cardholder website, by facsimile at 1-866-931-7874, electronically at [agent@rushcard.com](mailto:agent@rushcard.com) or you may write to the Program at UniRush LLC, P.O. Box 42482, Cincinnati, OH 45242. If you withdraw your consent we will mail paper versions of all Statements to you for no additional cost excluding monthly paper statements. Unless you request to receive monthly paper statements, the monthly paper statements will not be mailed to you. You may request to receive paper monthly statements be mailed to you at a cost of $1.00 per statement by visiting our website at [www.rushcard.com](http://www.rushcard.com/), calling us at 1-866-787-4227, emailing electronically at [agent@rushcard.com](mailto:agent@rushcard.com) or you may write to the Program at UniRush LLC, P.O. Box 42482, Cincinnati, OH 45242. If you have withdrawn your consent and you desire to give consent, you may contact us by any of the means noted above to consent for electronic delivery of information.

RushCard, UniRush, Pay Your Own Way, Rush Unlimited, RushCard Live, and RushGoals are registered trademarks of UniRush, LLC. Rise to Thrive, 24k RushCard, Carbon RushCard, Edge RushCard, Gloss RushCard, Midnight RushCard, Sequin KLS RushCard, and Suede KLS RushCard are trademarks of UniRush, LLC. All other trademarks, service marks and other registered marks are the property of their respective owners. 

Rushcard meets the Visa Clear Prepaid standards for clearly communicated fees and great consumer protections

Copyright 2015 UniRush, LLC. All Rights Reserved.
